Magical Maladies

somethingwicked

previous page next page

Chapter 1

Author's Notes:

This is my first attempt at a multi-chapter story, so please read and tell me what you think!

Wednesday, August 7

Dear Diary,

Last year, Hermione gave me this diary for my birthday. I found it a few days ago in the drawer of my desk, and decided to try it out. Writing in diaries is supposedly supposed to help you in relieving your feelings or whatever. Anyway, here goes:

“Ginevra Molly Weasley! Get up this instant! I swear; I don’t know where you get it. When I was your age, I was up at the crack of dawn, helping my mother. You, you’re just-” screamed my mother from the kitchen. I groaned and pulled the pillow over my head, blocking out the unwanted noise. It was the summer for god sakes; I had every right to stay in bed as late as I want.

“GINEVRA!” screeched my mother for the third time. I groaned once again. Not being able to ignore it any longer, I threw the covers off of me and ambled towards the bathroom, only to find that someone was already in it. Grumbling incoherently to myself, I banged my fist on the door and threatened to bat-bogey hex whoever was in there if they didn’t hurry up. Instantly, the door swung open, and guess who walks out? None other than Harry Potter, of course. I literally gasped and hit into the wall behind me. He took in my tousled hair, too-small tank, my old sweats, and smiled.

“Good morning, Ginny. I see you’re up early,” he said.

“Err, hi Harry. What are you doing up so early? I’m only up because my mum was screeching at me,” I replied.

He grinned. “I heard. I’m normally a morning person. Don’t like to sleep much.”

“Wow, I think sleeping is my next favorite thing after Quidditch. Well, I’ll meet you downstairs for breakfast. Let me just get cleaned up.” I said. He nodded and went down the stairs. I walked into the bathroom. After performing my morning necessities, I walked back into my room, and decided what to wear for the day. Deciding on a pair of jeans and t-shirt, I brushed my hair and walked out of the room and onto the top of the stairs where my mother had placed a horrid pink and orange throw rug, apparently of her own doings. Giving it a look of disgust, I stepped onto it… and away I fell, down two flights of stairs. THUMP, BAM…”ouch! Ouch!” HARRY! WATCH OUT! BAM!

Yes, I tumbled down the stairs, and straight into Harry, perfect right? To make it worse, I didn’t only hit into him, but I landed on top of him. Obviously, I jumped up as fast as I could, only to fall back again. Apparently, I had sprained my ankle or something, because whatever it was, I couldn’t stand up.

“Ginny, are you ok?” he asked, attempting to fix his lopsided glasses.

“Yeah, I think I just sprained my ankle or something. It’s nothing.”

Upon hearing my fall, Mum, Fred, George, Ron, and Hermione all rushed out of the kitchen.

“Harry, just what do you think you’re doing to my sister?!” was Ron’s only concern. Thankfully, Hermione told him to shut up and stop being so daft.

“I fell down the stairs, tumbled into Harry, and apparently I sprained my ankle and can’t get up. Could someone help me up, please?”

“Here I got it,” said Harry. He slid out form under me, picked up, then laid me on the couch. Wow, the last time I imagined Harry picking me up it was under totally different circumstances. Anyway, I looked up to see Mum, Fred, and George all looking as if they had just seen a ghost.

“What’s wrong? I just sprained my ankle. Mum could heal it in a second,” I said.

Mum walked over to me and placed her hand on my ankle, feeling the bone. I winced, and she said, “Ginny, it’s broken.”

“Oh, well, ok, can’t you heal that too?”

“Not really. This isn’t just any broken ankle, that’s why it’s not so painful. I think, and I hope dearly that I am not correct, that you have a something called ‘The Broken Love Bone’,” she said, her face very grave. Upon hearing this, Hermione gasped, Fred and George nodded their heads sadly, and Ron put his face in his hands. Apparently, Harry and I were the only ones who had no idea what that was.

“What’s that?” we both asked simultaneously.

Hermione was the one who explained this time. “Ginny, a broken love bone means that whichever bone was broken, which in your case is your ankle, will not heal until you fall in love. It a curse that Aphroditus the First placed on all wizard kind, after the woman he loved deserted him. Your ankle will not heal until you fall in love, and not just any type of love, it has to be genuine and mutual from both sides.”

“You’re not bloody serious are you? Wait what’s the difference between a love bone and just a regular bone? You might be wrong. What am I going to do? There’s a fat chance of me ever falling in love if I’m strapped to a bloody bed all day, don’t you think?” I was hyperventilating, and I began seeing stars.

“We know it’s a broken love bone because it was broken at precisely the same spot which all love bones are supposed to break. Also, you broke it, by tumbling into someone form the opposite gender, the same way a love bone usually breaks,” replied Hermione.

‘This is not bloody happening to me! What am I going to do? If I can’t find someone I like while I’m up on both feet, do you think I’m, going to find someone while I’m stuck on my bed? Mum!” I wailed.

“Ginny, calm down. Look, I’m pretty sure I read of a spell that can determine your true love somewhere; I just have to find it. So look, just calm down, rest, and believe me, it’ll be over faster than you think,” Hermione said.

Yeah right.

Table of contents

Introduction
Chapter 1
Chapter 2
Chapter 3
Chapter 4

previous page start next page

Magical Maladies

somethingwicked

previous page next page

Chapter 2

Author's Notes:

Second chapter….hope you enjoy it.

Thursday, August 8

Dear Diary,

Today I got up around ten in the morning and was contemplating what I was going to do with the rest of my life with a broken ankle. Let me tell you, the prospects did not look good. I guess I could get one of those cast things and use the crutchy or crutching or whatever those muggles use. I would look ridiculous though. Anyway, back to this morning, so I was lying on my bed when someone knocked gently on the door. I knew it wasn’t Hermione because she usually barges right in, my brothers usually bang on the door with their fists as if I was deaf, and mum and dad both call my name and then open the door, so I guessed it was Harry. Anyway, it did turn out to be Harry coming to apologize. Yes, apologize. It was the cutest thing ever. He walked in, both hands stuck deep into his pockets, looking down at the floor. He looked just like a little boy who did something wrong and is afraid to tell his mother. So he walked in and leaned on my closet, looking unsure whether or not to sit on my bed. I told him to come sit next me, and he sat at the edge of my bed, careful not to touch my ankle.

“Hey Gin-,” Isn’t that the cutest nickname ever? I almost melted on the spot when he called me that. “I just wanted to apologize for breaking your ankle or whatever, because technically it is my fault because you know it wouldn’t have been a love bone if you didn’t hit into someone from the opposite gender, who would be me, and I’m sorry.” At this point, I think Harry actually blushed. Weird. I thought I was the one who usually blushes.

“Harry! Don’t apologize! It was that blasted rug and my own clumsiness that made me fall! You just happened to be there. Actually, I’m the one who should be apologizing for hitting into you. I really am sorry for that; I know I’m not exactly the lightest thing.”

Harry chuckled at that. “Don’t worry; you didn’t hurt me a bit. You actually are pretty light.”

I giggled. “Well excuse me, mister macho man, I thought I hurt you.”

He laughed again, and we continued talking for a little bit after that. I didn’t realize how easy it is to talk to him. Besides being insanely handsome, he actually has a pretty good personality. After a while, Mum called up to Harry to tell him it was time for breakfast.

“Do you want me to carry you downstairs or do you want me to bring you something up? I broke your ankle, so I’ll be your slave,” he said jokingly. Hmm, he’ll be my slave, huh?

I laughed. “So you’re my slave? Ok then, carry me down the stairs, place me on the couch, come back and clean my room, then wash the dishes, scrub the floors, and then after that maybe I’ll give you a break,” I said laughingly.

“Ok then, your wish, my command.” And he actually leaned down and picked me up!

“Harry! I was joking! Mum is going to bring me something right now! Put me down!” I said.

“Nope. I’m taking you downstairs.”

“Harry!”

He didn’t even bother looking down this time. What could I do but lay back in his arms?

He took me down stairs and laid me down on the sofa. Then he actually walked into the kitchen, got me a tray loaded with eggs, pancakes, and coffee, and place it on my lap. Isn’t that so sweet?

“Now eat,” he commanded me, and walked into the kitchen to get his own food. Hermione and mum walked out of the kitchen, both with dumbfounded looks on their faces.

“Did Harry actually take you down the stairs and bring you food?” asked Hermione.

“Yes, well Harry is such a gentleman,” said Mum.

Oh god, I could tell by the dreamy look in my mum’s eyes that she was already planning our wedding. Suddenly I became defensive.

“What’s wrong with that? He just felt bad for me and didn’t want me to stay alone upstairs,” I said.

“Aww,” was Hermione’s reply. Grr, that makes me so mad.

After my mother got over Harry’s “gentlemanliness”, she began fussing over my ankle, which surprisingly hadn’t swollen at all. Hermione told me it was because it wasn’t a regular break, and wouldn’t have most of the characteristics of a normal broken bone. Actually besides the pain, there were no other similarities. Mum placed an enchanted ice pack on it, which numbed the pain almost immediately.

“Hey, Hermione, didn’t you say that you read of some spell that could determine your true love?” I asked her.

“Yes, I’m pretty sure I did, but I didn’t find it yet. Don’t worry though, I’m looking. The only thing I’m afraid of is that half these love spells don’t work, and if the spell that I find actually does work, it must either be extremely complicated, or extremely ancient. If it wasn’t everyone would be using it, correct?” she asked me.

“I guess that’s true. But if we do find it and its complicated or whatever, you’ll be able to do it? Like there is some possible way of casting it right?”

Hermione smiled. “Once I find it, I’ll be able to manage it.” Of course.

Later on in the afternoon, we (as in Ron, Harry, Hermione, and me) were all sitting in the living room talking. Thankfully, it was raining outside and they couldn’t go play Quidditch as they were planning to do, and leave me alone by myself. At some point of the conversation, we ran out of things to say, and just sat looking around us. To liven things up, I proposed a game.

“Hey guys, want to play truth or dare?” I asked.

Harry and Hermione agreed at once, but for some reason Ron was reluctant.

“Why don’t you want to play, Ron? Do you have anything you want to hide from us? We already know who you like, so there’s no use of hiding.” Harry said. Hermione blushed delicately at this point, and as usual, Ron’s ears turned red. Dumb, clueless people.

“That’s not the reason I don’t want to play. I just think it’s a pointless game, that’s all,” Ron said.

“Ron stop being so stubborn and play with us,” asked Hermione sweetly.

“Ugh, fine ok,” said Ron.

“How come you only agree when Hermione asks?” I asked.

“Shut up Ginny.”

Anyway, the game only started getting interesting when Harry dared Hermione to kiss Ron. Since this was a magical truth or dare game, you couldn’t refuse a dare because if you did, your ears would turn neon pink, and wouldn’t be returned back to normal until the dare was fulfilled. The things wizards come up with…

So of course, the blushing began again and Ron leaned in to kiss Hermione… well lets say they took much longer then expected. They both emerged looking quite abashed at their actions. They wouldn’t look at each other straight in the eye for the rest of the game. Now this is where the interesting part is. In retaliation, my dearest brother Ron dared Harry to kiss me. KISS ME!!! Could you believe it? Harry, Hermione, and I just sort of stared at Ron for a good minute when he dared us. I daresay we looked quite ridiculous with our dumbfounded expressions. So of course, Harry had to kiss me unless he wanted his ears to turn pink… which wouldn’t be good. What was Ron thinking?!! What happened to being all big brotherly and "protecting my virtue" or whatever? Daring his best friend to kiss his sister isn’t exactly protecting my virtue, now is it? I honestly didn’t know what to do when he said that. I looked at Hermione as if she could stop it or something, but she still looked dumbfounded. I had no choice. I looked at Harry who was blushing quite profusely and nodded. He leaned in…

Now I’m back in bed at night. I think I’m still blushing from the aftereffects of what happened with Harry today. It was so unexpected… but the kiss felt so natural, like we’ve been doing it forever. I thought it would be just a quick peck or something, but we actually took some time. I honestly still can’t believe we did that. I’m unsure whether to be mad at Ron, or thankful he did that. Wow. Ok, I got to go. Hermione is telling me to “stop scratching away at my bloody diary”.

Table of contents

Introduction
Chapter 1
Chapter 2
Chapter 3
Chapter 4

previous page start next page

Magical Maladies

somethingwicked

previous page next page

Chapter 3

Author's Notes:

Here we go, third chapter. Oh and one more thing, I would really like to thank all my reviewers for your awesome reviews. You guys are amazing! I love knowing what my readers think. So as always, please review!

Friday, August 9

Dear Diary,

This morning I got up feeling extremely nauseous and woozy. I was freezing and couldn’t stop shivering. Thankfully, mum came straight into my room when she heard me moving around in my bed.

“Ginny, are you ok?” she asked. I guess I looked really pale or something.

“I think I caught the flu or something. I feel nauseous and I’m extremely cold.”

She placed her hand on my forehead. “You have a fever. You’re forehead is burning up.” Great. Fever and a broken ankle.

At that moment Hermione walked in. Apparently she had just woken up because she was still wearing her pajamas and carrying a cup of coffee.

“What’s wrong with Ginny?” she asked Mum.

“She has a fever,” Mum replied.

Hermione put the cup down on the dresser. “Ginny, is your ankle swollen more than normal?” she asked. Mum bent down and lifted up the blanket off my ankle. Sure enough it was redder and more swollen then I had ever seen it.

Hermione nodded her head. “Is there anything else that hurts you?”

“Yeah, my left pinky and thumb are also bothering me a bit. They have this like dull, throbbing pain, I don’t know why. They were fine yesterday.”

“I know why. This isn’t a regular fever. Its one of the symptoms of a broken love bone. You’re fever is going to get pretty bad. There’s nothing to do but just wait it out,” she said. I groaned and burrowed my head under my pillow.

Oh no. This cannot be happening to me. What have I done to deserve such a horrible fate? Why am I cursed this way? WHY? Ok, I’m done being a drama queen.

I heard Hermione speaking to mum. “She has to find her true love soon. Already, the symptoms are getting worse. Something needs to be done.”

I threw the pillow off of me with such force that it hit Hermione in the head. “Wait. What? There’s a time limit for this thing? Like what, if I don’t find my true love soon or something, I’m going to die?” I was becoming hysterical now.

“Ginny, no! There is no time limit, its just that the longer you take to find your true love, the worse you’re symptoms will get. For example after your flu goes away, another will come and each time it’ll get worse. That’s all I mean. But there’s no recorded accounts of anyone ever dying of a love bone, so don’t worry.”

Oh. That’s supposed to make me feel better. I won’t die, but I’ll just keep getting worse and worse flues.

So after Hermione told us the wonderful news of me having a terrible fever, Mum brought up a rather scrumptious breakfast. I guess she was feeling bad for me, considering now that I’m confined to my bed. I decided that some sort of action needs to be done. Obviously, I will never find “my true love” if I’m in bed all day, right? The only person I can like in this house and who’ll like me back is Harry, and I don’t see that happening anytime soon. Now what? How will I ever meet someone? Should I try to make Harry like me back or just forget about him? Did Hermione find that love spell and will it work?

Giving myself a major headache with all my unanswerable questions, I decided to give myself a break and not think about my current situation right now. After finishing up my breakfast, I leaned my head against the pillows and fell into a deep sleep.

“I got it!” screamed Hermione from the top of the stairs. Everyone turned around to look at her.

“Got what?” I asked from the sofa, the current location I had been moved to.

“It took me forever to find it, but I got it!” she said.

“Got what?” repeated Harry.

“The love spell!” she said, her face alight with happiness.

I dropped the book I was reading. Is it possible there is one ray of sunshine in my miserable life, just one iota of happiness? Will I be cured of this miserable blight? Is it possible?! Wow, I am such a drama queen. Anyway, back to Hermione.

Of course, when she said that, everyone immediately jumped out of their seats.

“You found it? My baby will finally be cured!” cried Mum.

“Good job, Hermione!” said Harry.

“Wow, you’re even more brilliant than I thought you were,” said Ron. This of course made Hermione blush, which triggered Ron’s blush, and the circle of never-ending blushes began. Will these people ever get a clue?

Hermione went to sit on the sofa by my feet and opened the notebook she was holding.

“Ok, as I predicted, this spell is both extremely ancient and extremely difficult. I found it in a book of love spells that the Renaldi family, an ancient pureblood family, used to pass around from one witch to another. The actual book is kept in the Museum of Magic, but excerpts from the book are placed in the Department of Archives in the Ministry of Magic for public-viewing. What is strange about the spell is that for it to actually work properly, the person it is being cast on has to drink a potion. The potion itself is ancient, although not very difficult to make. Since I already made the potion, all we have to do is actually cast the spell,” said Hermione.

We all stared at her in awe. “Wow, thanks Hermione. I’m so touched that you did all that for me,” I said, smiling appreciatively at her.

“Yeah well, Hermione is naturally a very caring person,” said Ron. Jeez Ron, could you stop with the cheesy compliments?

I guess Mum couldn’t express her gratitude in any way except pulling Hermione into a bone-crushing hug that left her looking slightly disheveled.

“Guys, honestly, it was nothing. I enjoyed doing this. Now let’s get to work. I already made the potion, so all we have to do is make Ginny drink it and wait an hour before casting the spell. When the spell is cast, a single scroll of parchment will appear with the name of your love on it. However, if you already know who your true love is and the love is mutual between you both, nothing will appear at all.”

“Well, at least we know that won’t happen. I have no idea who my true love is.” I said.

Hermione smiled mysteriously. “You never know,” she said. What’s that supposed to mean? Anyway after having the potion unceremoniously shoved down my throat-it tasted horrible by the way, like troll boogies- and having waited the mandatory hour, Hermione got ready to perform the spell. Now that it was actually time, I began to feel anxious. What if I had no true love and the spell didn’t work at all? I was also scared to actually find out who it was. As Hermione prepared to say the spell, my family gathered around me and Mum held my hand.

“Amore appearus,” Hermione muttered. The last thing I saw were Harry’s emerald eyes staring at me before I passed out.

Table of contents

Introduction
Chapter 1
Chapter 2
Chapter 3
Chapter 4

previous page start next page

Magical Maladies

somethingwicked

previous page

Chapter 4

Author's Notes:

Last chapter!! Sorry for taking so long, I was just so busy the last few weeks.. Anyway, hope you enjoy!

Chapter 4

Friday, August 9

Dear Diary,

Hermione told me that I had been out for a whole half hour. I guess Mum got really worried or something, because when I woke up an old Healer with little tufts of white hair on his head was peering at me over his spectacles. At first I couldn’t focus my vision and everything seemed a little blurry at the edges, but after rubbing my eyes a few times they went back to normal.

“Ahh, Miss Wellen, I see you’ve decided to join us,” said the old Healer.

Even in my half-groggy state I managed to correct him.

“It’s Weasley,” I said.

“Yes, yes I’m sure it is,” he said absentmindedly, whilst taking my pulse. He turned around to Mum and said, “Your little girl is absolutely fine. Fainting can occur when the person is very fatigued, or dehydrated, so it’s best to let her rest and provide her with fluids constantly.”

Grr. I hate people calling me “little girl”.

Mum nodded and her hands flitted pointlessly around my blankets, trying to fix them for me. “Is there nothing to give her?” Mum asked.

“No, that won’t be necessary. All Miss Wayne needs is a good, long nap and a bowl of chicken soup,” he said merrily, patting my head.

Ok, I am seriously not liking this guy. How hard is it to remember “Weasley”?!?!

My mother nodded again and led the Healer out of my room. I settled back on the pillows and rested my head against the headboard. I felt like I was forgetting something… I gasped. “HERMIONE!!!” I screamed.

I heard someone running up the stairs and my door burst open. Hermione came running in, with Mum close behind her.

“Ginny, are you ok? Do you feel faint again? Should I call the Healer?” Mum asked.

“No, I’m fine. Just tell me what happened after I fainted. Did the paper come out? What did it say? Whose name!?” I asked impatiently.

“Ahh,” my mother said. That is not a good sign. I turned to Hermione and gave her an expectant look.

“Well?” I asked her.

Hermione sat at the edge of my bed. “Ginny, there was no paper. Nothing appeared when I said the spell,” she said.

I stared unbelievingly at her. I just could not comprehend her words. “I’m sorry, what? I didn’t understand what you said.”

“There was no paper. Nothing at all. There was nothing that said the name of your true love or anything. This means two things. Either I performed the spell wrong, which I highly doubt, or you already know your true love, which is more probable,” said Hermione.

“I don’t think it’s either. Of course you didn’t do the spell wrong, you never do anything wrong, and I know I don’t know my true love because if I did I would have been walking long before now so there must be some other reason.” I said.

Hermione stared at me. “Ginny, are you absolutely sure there is no one that could possibly be your true love? No one at all?” Hermione asked.

“Hermione, you know there is no one except…” I said, but was interrupted by a knock at the door.

“Come in!” called Hermione. The door opened and Harry walked in.

This cannot be a bloody coincidence. Like honestly, this is just too perfect timing.

I gave Hermione a look. Apparently she understood because she said “oh” softly and patted my hand. Harry came and sat on the chair of my desk.

“Hey, Ginny. How are you?” he asked me politely. Damn those piercing green eyes of his.

“I’m fine. Harry. Thanks for asking.” Why was everything suddenly so stiff and formal?

“So, no paper appeared?” he asked in a conversational tone.

I hung my head. “Unfortunately not. I don’t know what to do now.”

He sighed. “Doesn’t that mean that you already know your true love?” What is it with those green eyes that feel like he’s boring into my very skin?! I feel like he could see what I’m thinking!

“Yeah, it does, but that’s not the case for me. I honestly do not know or have any idea who my 'true love' is,” I replied.

“Ahh, that could be a problem. Which is why I researched some more about this love spell and whatnot,” he said.

I think my jaw dropped open. Literally. Harry did research for me? As in Harry Potter?! *sniff* I’m becoming emotional.

“You did what?” I croaked. I looked over at Hermione, who had the same awestruck look on her face.

“Well, after you passed out, and it was obvious no paper appeared, I decided that there must be some solution to this problem. It’s extremely simple, really. Do you want to hear it?”

“Yes! Of course. What is it?” I said.

“All you have to do is take Veritaserum. When asked who your true love is, Veritaserum will force you to say it, because although you may not know it, subconsciously you do know who it is. I’ve read about it. It’s true. Then once you do say it, all we have to do is go to that person and make them to do the same thing, and it’s almost a hundred percent chance that he will say that you’re his true love also.”

“Of course!” Hermione said. “That’s genius!”

I could only nod weakly. I didn’t want to get my hopes up for the second time today in thinking I might actually find out who it is. I did remember though to thank Harry.

“Harry, wow, thank you so much. No one would have ever thought of that. I really appreciate it. What could I ever do to repay you?”

He blushed. “It was nothing,” he mumbled.

Hermione rushed downstairs to tell my mother. I could hear her from my room exclaiming how she knew Harry was always a genius and then rushing out to the Apothecary to buy Veritaserum.

In due time, my mother was back with a bottle of clear, odorless Veritaserum. I was more nervous this time than last time because I could tell this was it. This was the time I would actually find out who my true love is. Oh god.

Mum put a few drops onto a spoon and held to my mouth. Hermione came and sat at the edge of my bed with an expectant look. I saw Harry edge out of my room.

“Harry, wait!” I said. “Why are you leaving?”

“Because this is a private moment for you. I'll just wait downstairs.”

“Harry, don’t be silly. We would have never done this without you. Stay here,” I said.

He blushed, but came and sat on the chair again. Once again, Mum held the spoon into my mouth and this time I swallowed the liquid.

Mum turned to Hermione. “You ask her. I’m too anxious.”

Hermione nodded. “Ginevra Molly Weasley, who is your true love?”

I answered automatically. “Harry James Potter.”

I don’t believe it. I don’t believe it. I don’t believe it. Did I just say “Harry Potter”?! And he heard me?! Oh my god. Oh my god.

There was a deathly silence. If this hadn’t been such a serious situation, it would have been quite comical. Mum had a queer look on her face as if she was mixed up between being extremely happy and extremely shocked at the same time. Hermione had a tiny smile on her face as if saying “Ha! I knew it!” And Harry… I was too scared to look in the direction. I didn’t know what to do with my eyes. Should I keep looking down at my hands or look at Mum, or what? I was desperately avoiding looking in his direction. Finally, Hermione broke the silence.

“Harry?” Hermione asked.

Ok, I had to look. I couldn’t take the suspense. I turned and look at him. He was extremely pale… and he had a sort of half grin on his face. Uhh, why was he grinning?! Did this seem like a funny situation to him? I just humiliated myself in front of the love of my life, my best friend, and my mother! Besides that annoying yet extremely adorable grin on his face, he was staring at me. Like he wasn’t even blinking. Just… staring.

“Harry?” Hermione said again.

Finally he stopped staring at me with those x-ray eyes of his. His grin was steadily getting bigger. It was almost a complete smile now.

“Yes, Hermione?” he said. His voice was rough.

“For this to completely work, we need you to take Veritaserum too. So, you know, we could ask you the same question.” Hermione said.

Ok now he was really smiling. Like a huge smile. “No need,” he said simply. “I already know.”

I could feel my heart shattering into ten thousand million little pieces. The tears started welling up in my eyes and immediately I started sniffing. My mum looked at me with shock. I never cry. It’s just the fact that he said it so simply, so nonchalantly, I couldn’t take it anymore. I brushed away the tears, but they just kept coming harder and harder. There was a gaping hole in my chest where my heart used to be. I didn’t think I cared about him this much. I mean I knew, but… wow.

My mum started whispering into my ear about how I would find someone better and that I was better than that and all that nonsense but Hermione tugged my mother’s hand and pulled her away.

“Harry and Ginny need to talk. Now,” she said.

Mum nodded and on her way out of the door she stopped. “Harry…”

I looked at him, to see his reaction, but all he did was nod. I don’t feel like talking to him right now. I have embarrassed myself more than once today. I am not the type of girl to show my feelings to everyone like this. Crying was strictly allowed only at night, in my own bed when I was alone. And saying my crush to everyone was definitely not allowed…

Hermione closed the door after her as she walked out. And then Harry came and sat right next to me on the bed. He actually had the nerve to sit next me! If I wasn’t scared of having my wand taken away by the Ministry, I would have hexed him right then and there.

“Ginny…” he started, but I interrupted him.

“Harry, you don’t need to tell me anything. Don’t feel obligated to comfort me or anything. Neither you nor I should blame you for the way you feel. Its ok, I understand,” I said. That was dignified, right?

Harry groaned. “Could you please let me say what I want to say?” he asked.

Whoah. Excuse me.

“Go ahead.” I said.

“Ginny, you totally misunderstood me. When I said 'I already know'. I meant there was no point of taking Veritaserum, because I already knew my true love,” he said.

“I know.” I replied.

“I mean you. You’re my true love,” he said.

I don’t remember what it was I did exactly at this point, because after he said that everything was a blur. I’m sure it involved gasping and hyperventilating though…

I looked up at him with my eyes wide open.

“Do you really mean that?” I asked.

Apparently, he didn’t think words were good enough to express his answer, because instead he scooped me up - am I really that light? - and kissed me. It was absolute and total bliss. Try as I might, I would not be able to describe it here, so I’m not even going to bother. So he scooped me up, and laid my back against the dresser and proceeded to kiss me. It might have been unromantic at the time, but I had to interrupt our incredible kiss to tell him something.

“Harry?” I said.

“Hmmph?” He looked extremely put out about being interrupted - believe me so was I, but this was urgent.

“My ankle is healed,” I said.

He smiled. “I love you.” And he went right back to kissing me.

There you have it, the last chapter of Magical Maladies!! Totally fluff, i know, but I live for H/G fluff so… Anyway, I hope you enjoyed it, and as always, don't forget to review!!!

Table of contents

Introduction
Chapter 1
Chapter 2
Chapter 3
Chapter 4

previous page start